

+91 9877178891 | navjotmanak01@gmail.com | Hoshiarpur, Punjab(India)

OBJECTIVE

I'm thrilled to have the chance to work for a forward-thinking organization that promotes innovation, where I can actively contribute to innovative projects and develop my career. I'm excited to learn about different opportunities in the tech sector and to show how my experience and energy align with the goals of your business.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Technology in Computer Science & Eng. 2020 - 2024

Punjabi University Patiala, Punjab (INDIA)

CGPA - 89.6

Intermediate (PSEB 12th) 2019 - 2020

Residentail Meritorious School Jalandhar, Punjab (INDIA)

PERCENTAGE - 92.22

Metriculation (PSEB 10th) 2017 - 2018

Senior Secndary School Mehlanwali, Punjab (INDIA)

PERCENTAGE - 82.77

WORK EXPERIENCE

Excellence Technology

January 2024 - May 2024

- MERN Stack
- Front-End Development (HTML, CSS, JavaScript), Collaboration and Teamwork, Testing and Debugging, Reporting and Documentation

Numetry Technolgies

July 2024 - Present

- Software Developer Intern
- HTML,CSS,JAVASCRIPT,REACTJS,SPRINGBOOT

Excellence Technology

June 2023 - July 2023

- Front End Development
- 6 Week Industrial Training

PROJECTS

· Safar- Tour and Travel Website

July 2023

Safar is a dynamic travel website crafted with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, offering seamless navigation and user-friendly features for travelers to explore destinations, book activities, accommodations, and plan memorable journeys.

• POKEDOX September 2023

Utilized **ReactJS**, **HTML**, **CSS**, and JS to build the ReactJS Pokedox web application, empowering users to search and explore information about various Pokemon in an organized and visually appealing manner, enhancing user experience and engagement.

• Sahand Estate Website

January 2024

Sahand Estate is a modern real estate website built with the MERN stack (MongoDB, Express.js, React, Node.js). It offers advanced property search and secure user authentication in a responsive design for all devices.

OTHER

- Technical Skils: HTML, CSS, C/C++, JavaScript, ReactJS, Java (Basics), SQI (Basics)
- Other Skills: UI/UX Designing (Figma), Graphics Arts using Canva (Poster, Presentations etc.)
- Soft Skills: Problem Solving, Team Management, Creativity, Communication skills.
- Languages: English (Fluent), Hindi (Fluent), Punjabi (Fluent)